Contact

kunstroger41@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/roger-kunst-49bb22205 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

JavaScript Unity

React Native

Roger Kunst

Full Stack Developer at Self Employed Woodbridge

Summary

I am a senior full stack web and mobile developer with extensive experience. Supported by skills developed in my degree, I have developed skills in observation, problem solving and group collaboration. Presently skill in technologies such as HTML5/CSS3, Javascript, Angular, Node.js, React/Redux, React Native, C#/C++, Java, Unity, several CSS libraries, and MySQL, MongoDB. These skills are just the start of my journey in this industry, and I have plenty of room to grow and develop in my current technologies and skills, and well as new ones.

Experience

Self Employed Full Stack Developer February 2021 - Present (3 months)

DEXSTR

Front-end Lead Developer October 2018 - January 2021 (2 years 4 months)

- Lead front-end developer in an agile environment.
- Code improvements (ES6, Gulp tasks, code reviews, pair programming)
- Development of new functionalities
- Always looking for ways to improve the UI performances
- Deployment management (Jenkins, Docker)
- Task automation (Gulp)
- UX/UI improvements
- Technical environment : AngularJS, MongoDB, Java, Spring, Electron, NodeJS, Angular-Material, HTML, CSS, Gulp, Bower, NPM,GIT

DECASOFT

Full Stack Developer May 2015 - September 2018 (3 years 5 months)

- Development of a internal reporting application now used by the whole company.
- Technical environment: MEAN architecture (MongoDB, Express, AngularJS, NodeJS), Angular Material design, Grunt, Bower, NPM, GIT
- Consultant at "MiPiH" as a JEE engineer
- Agile processes : Kanban board / Scrum / TDD / Pair programming

Capgemini

Full Stack Web Developer July 2013 - March 2015 (1 year 9 months)

- Web application Development
- Design of technical solutions
- Maintenance under operationnal conditions (KSH, pl/sql scripts)
- Estimation of the new functionnalities
- Management of the application's deployments (jenkins, shell)
- New developers training
- Setting up SOAP webservices
- Technical environment : Java, Struts, SQL, PL/SQL, KSH, Weblogic Portal, JSP, JS, HTML, CSS, SVN

Education

General Assembly

Computer Software Engineering · (2020 - 2021)

Eastern Michigan University

Bachelor's degree, Business Administration and Management, General · (2009 - 2013)